x-cart.com 2011-06-25

# Qualiteam Privacy Policy

"New web-site from scratch" means you want us to create a web-site of any kind and make it ready to go live. Since creation of a web-site from the very beginning is quite a complex process it may include multiple stages like:  
• web-design creation and integration;  
• integration of a pre-made design template into selected platform;  
• filling in the product catalog;  
• developing desired features;  
• installation onto the web-hosting;  
• etc.

Select this service if you want us to customize software you are using as platform for your web-site. This means adding new and changing existing features of the platform software.

You have a web-site already, but does not like it or want to improve its appearance. We can create a new look for your existing web-site, adapt your current design to make it more "e-commerce" and suitable for shopping cart software.

You do not want to change design of your web-site a lot, but want to enhance it a bit by adding some new graphic design elements, improve layout of pages, set new styles and fonts, etc.

This service is useful for startups companies and companies willing to change the way their customers recognize them by logo and corporate style.

You have a web-site which visitors recognize by unique and outstanding design and want to integrate some software (e.g. shopping cart software) into it seamlessly.

key pages include home page, product details, products listings (categories, manufacturers, search results), cart and checkout pages

for example, e-mail notifications, image pop-up window

Consultation on small modifications of the software: possible if the required changes take about 30 minutes to describe

Consultation on medium modifications of the software: possible if the required changes take about an hour to describe

Application of a patch fixing a bug in X-Cart/LiteCommerce store (patches themselves are provided for free)

Additional services costing more than the other tasks or not included into original tech support duties

Installation tasks fulfilled within tech support service

Installation of any 3rd-party web-software like blog, forum, cms etc.

Installation & configuration of server software: Apache Web Server, NginX Web Server, PHP, MySQL

SSL certificate installation (including CSR generation and assistance in purchasing)

Zero-downtime transfer of online store to a different hosting

Transfer of online store along with extensive custom code modifications

Transfer of Sales-n-Stats to a different hosting

Transfer of LiteCommerce ASPE to a different hosting

Performance benchmarking of Smarty, PHP, MySQL along with general X-Cart and web server speed up measures

Application-focused server configuration and performance speed-up

Check of an online store's readiness for indexing by major search engines

Check and fix of possible web server and software components security vulnerabilities

General questions: explanations of our policies such as support-point system basics, ticket processing rules, etc; description of our services, assistance on HelpDesk and forum usage, and so on.

Consultation on software functionalities, explanation of existing functionalities and features

Product waranty issues: bugs revealing and further providing of patches

Problem-solving which involves investigation on client's store

Problem-solving which involves investigation on client's store and server

Problem-solving which involves code debugging and protracted debug data monitoring

X-Cart SEO enchancements: SEO-friendly URLs, custom TITLE and META tags for products, categories and static pages, robots.txt configuration, XML sitemap creation

Google Analytics installation service for X-Cart/LiteCommerce stores

Advice on basic usage of X-Cart/LiteCommerce features

Assistance/consultation on software configuration issues or basic features/design modification. Available if the changes take less than 30 minutes to elaborate. Does not involve any changes on client's server.

Troubleshooting involving investigation on client's store and/or server

Troubleshooting involving investigation on client's server, code debugging and protracted debug data monitoring

Additional services not included into the list. Usually cost more that the specified tasks, therefore discussed with clients first.

The number of provided concepts on the first step. If none of the sketches is chosen, we will create a new set of sketches from a scratch one more time, based on your corrections and remarks.

Internet:

  * Website and Internet marketing
  * Email signature and email marketing

Printing purpose:

  * Stationery & Business cards
  * Signs & Billboards
  * Brochures & Flyers
  * Ads
  * Direct marketing & Postcards

The number of possible iterations for the chosen concept (in order to finalize details and produce the final outcome).

A vector image of your logo (meaning you can resize it as you like without compromising print quality and manipulate it should you ever need to make changes to your logo).

A high-definition raster format (used in various raster image editors).

A document specifying the CMYK model of a logo (along with PANTONE color table, if possible).

A document containing examples of logo usage in business cards, brochures, letter-heads, greeting cards, envelopes etc.

We will develop a graphic prototype of the flyout menu that can be used later during integration of the design with your store.

Currently we are supporting the following software:

  * WordPress
  * Drupal
  * Joomla!

We will be happy to help you with the installation, assistance on setting them up or troubleshooting. If you need an assistance on open-source 3rd party software (not even CMS), which is not listed above, feel free to contact us anyway. We will do our best to help you. Also, it will help us to understand what else we should add to the list of supporting software.

A consultation on the software installation/transfer/cloning basics

Investigation and resolution of the problems that occurred during a self-performed software installation/transfer/cloning

The installation cost will depend on the distribution package and on the complexity of the installation procedure itself

Apache, PHP, MySQL, Perl, etc.

A consultation on the upgrade basics

Investigation and resolution of the problems that occurred during a self-performed upgrade

The upgrade service estimation is provided free of charge

The upgrade service estimation is provided free of charge

The exact rate will depend on the customizations applied to the store and on the target server environment

Any solution for the website performance improvement offered as a result of the service will cost extra

Application-focused server configuration and performance speed-up

for X-Cart v4.3.2 and earlier

|  |  |  | Legal notices  
---  
Moneyback guarantee  
Quality policy  
Privacy policy  
Trademark policy  
Customization Agreement  
Software Development Agreement  
Graphic Design Agreement  
Affiliate agreement  
Technical Support Agreement  
| 

This Privacy Policy describes the types of information Qualiteam Corp ("we", "us") collects and how we use that information. If You do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use Qualiteam Products or Services ("Products or Services") and do not access the Qualiteam's websites located at [http://www.qtmsoft.com](http://www.qtmsoft.com/), [http://www.x-cart.com](http://www.x-cart.com/), [http://www.litecommerce.com](http://www.litecommerce.com/) ("Site", "Sites"). 

## Information We Collect

If You choose to use Products or Services, we may require You to provide contact and identity information, billing information, and other personal information as indicated on the Sites. Once You register on the Site, You are no longer anonymous to us. 

We collect and store the following information: 

  * Email address, physical contact information, and financial information;
  * Computer sign-on data, statistics on page views, traffic to and from Sites and ad data (all through cookies - You can take steps to disable cookies on Your browser, however this is likely to affect Your ability to use Sites);
  * Remote access codes to your server (we ask for this information if You register for a service that could not be provided without having such information);
  * Discussion board posts and other messages, including correspondence between us and You; and
  * General information regarding the Products or Services You have registered to receive.

We do not store the following information normally: 

  * Credit card information;
  * Access codes to providers of payment processing services;
  * Access codes to providers of domain registration services; and
  * Any information about your own clients.

Nevertheless we may store the information mentioned above if it is necessary for providing Service. 

## Our Use of Your Information

We use Your personal information to: 

  * provide Products and Services;
  * resolve disputes, calculate and collect fees, and troubleshoot problems;
  * verify users' identity and the information users provide;
  * encourage safe online experience and enforce our policies;
  * customize users' experience, analyze site usage, improve and measure interest in our services, and inform users about services and updates;
  * communicate administrative announcements when we need to provide users with information that may affect their use of Products or Services;
  * communicate marketing and promotional offers to our users;
  * provide customer service; and
  * perform other business activities as described when we collect the information.

As part of your registration for Products or Services on the Site, You agree that You may receive certain administrative communications from us, such as administrative announcements and customer service messages regarding Products or Services and products during the period that we provide Products or Services to You, and You will not be able to opt out of receiving such administrative communications. 

## Our Disclosure of Your Information

We do not sell or rent Your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without Your explicit consent. We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a listing or other content violates other's rights, or protect anyone's rights, property, or safety. We may also share personal information with: 

  * service providers who help with our business operations and assist in the delivery of Products or Services to our users. These service providers are under confidentiality agreements with us;
  * law enforcement or other government officials in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, violations of law, or as otherwise required by law.

## Accessing, Reviewing and Changing Your Personal Information

If you are registered to receive Products or Services, You can access, review and modify Your personal information at any time by logging into your Profile page located at [https://secure.qtmsoft.com](https://secure.qtmsoft.com/). 

We delete personal information when we no longer need it for the purposes we described earlier. We retain personal information as permitted by law to resolve disputes, enforce our policies, and help prevent bad guys from coming back. 

## Security

To prevent unauthorized access, promote data security, and encourage appropriate use of information, we use a variety of tools (encryption technologies, passwords, physical and electronic security, procedural safeguards) to assist in the protection of Your information. However, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet, so we make no guarantees. 

## Notification of Changes

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended terms on Sites. In the event of amendment, all terms shall become effective 30 days after they are initially posted to the Sites. Your continued use of Products or Services will constitute your acceptance of any changes or additions to this Privacy Policy. 

|
